

# NỀN TẢNG TUYỂN DỤNG NHÂN SỰ HÀNG ĐẦU VIỆT NAM

Ứng viên DAT L. | Nguồn tuyendung.topcv.vn





DAT L. Full Stack Developer

(c) [protected data]

(a) Male

protected@topcv.vn

(m) June 13, 1988

(%) [protected data]

(v) Danang, Vietnam



# **Objective**

I have over 8 years of experience as a full-stack programmer. It mean I really experienced on developing an application. From scratch into well-done application, production ready. It starting from requirement engineering, database design, back-end process, API, and also good-looking user interface. All build with quality priority. For me, providing high quality of work and precise estimation is must.



### **Education**

## UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY - THE UNIVERSITY OF **DANANG**

Oct 2006 - May 2011

Major: Information Technology

Project, scientific research: Quiz online system



### **Skills**

Back-end	PHP, NodeJS, Ruby on Rais, MySQL, PostgreSQL
Front-end	HTML/CSS, Javascript, jQuery, React, Twitter Bootstrap
Infrastructure	Docker, Vagrant, Linux server, Git, AWS, JIRA, Pivotal Tracker, Microservice



# Work experience

**VINABITS** Sep 2011 - May 2013

Web Developer

- Participate in the development of the company's project
- Full stack Joomla Developer.
- Technical Lead

**AGILITYIO** Aug 2013 - May 2019

### Full Stack Developer

- Participate in the development of the company's project
- Front-end developer
- Back-end developer
- Team Lead project (size 6-8 people)

#### **UOYMEDIA**

Jun 2019 - Present

CTO

- Technical Lead

#### **SELLERWIX**

Jun 2019 - Present

## Devops

- Technical Lead
- Devops developer



## **Projects**

FITMOO Nov 2013 - June 2014

Position: Frontend Developer

- A network where everything related to health and fitness could connect, plus the ability for fitness professionals and small businesses to make transactions online.
- https://fitmoo.com

WSRINSURANCE June 2014 - Sep 2014

Position: Team Lead project (size 4 people)

- Worley, Schilling & Randall Insurance is one of the leading independently-owned agencies in the southeast region. Revamp their official website so that it better reflects their brand and mission.
- http://wsrinsurance.com

MODAVANTI Oct 2014 - Feb 2015

Position: Backend Developer

- Implementing a re-branding and re-positioning of their site and to build it on the BigCommerce platform.
- https://modavanti.com

#### THE RELATED RENTALS BLOG

Mar 2015 - Jun 2015

Position: Team Lead project (size 6 people)

- The blog for Related Rentals.
- https://blog.relatedrentals.com

HINTMD Jul 2015 - Dec 2017

Position: Full Stack Developer

- HintMD is a subscription service that delivers professional skincare solutions to your door on a recurring basis.
- https://hintmd.com

WORLDROAMER Jan 2018 - May 2019

Position: Backend Developer

- WorldRoamer helps you travel and discover local destinations better. Book hotels in Southeast Asia & Japan, anytime and anywhere.
- https://www.worldroamer.com

SELLERWIX Jun 2019 - Present

Position: Devops

- Implement tool for seller with many platform like: WooCommerce, Shopify, Amazon...